do we have to use Kobe's 7:10
16 nothing 1726 oh my god I should go on
the discord on their 35 sup yo G there
we go so jacked really what up you're
not been working out okay they see that
not sue sue though you see these are my
values all right what up what up scope
is how many spokes guns alive sixty
sixty Scopus all right guys how many
you're happy to see me
Judy Scott Caan's now Wow we missed you
bro they're not saying they're happy to
see they just say oh good good good they
don't even know what I have planned for
today yeah oh now they're saying they're
happy
oh good I'm glad they're happy wait we
got a few more people cuz we have an
announcement today I'm not gonna say
it's a big announcement I'm not gonna
say it's good announcement but it is the
title does allude to what the
announcement is do we have a neon we do
can I hold me on oh here we go
perfect ah this is a neon that connected
up to my computer how many we go okay 86
we wait for a hundred yes it's a big
announcement um 89 91 guys don't like
psych up your friends or anything it's
not like you know that big of an
announcement no no no today's guys we
got the answer days and we're gonna do
something that's gonna help improve you
know how are you happy honest all right
how many us copies I wonder what for
Sammy's coffees you got Mandy 191 how
many of you 91 have you if you have any
on this is gonna make you
happy if you don't have a neon this is
gonna make you sad
96 93 going up and down out out out
so how many of them how many of them
have yachts could they raise their hand
let's say like see half of them have
feelings all right so that's like you
know 45 over 91 so you guys we're gonna
be happy and then the other ones are
gonna be you know the one - is gonna be
sad right yeah
don't have one yet oh so Young's are an
appreciating asset just like Tesla Model
3 let me explain to you what that means
okay so you can look at appreciation
like this this axis represents time and
this axis represents price and Furion's
cost this much now a depreciating asset
would go down but an appreciating asset
is going to go up so this one no one
one-on-one partner this is the perfect
time for this enough yeah so eons are an
appreciating asset and using this d20
here we're going to determine exactly
how much they're going to appreciate
today and it's oh my god is that a 20
that's literally a wait is that a 20 or
14 that's right it lets you know what
let's call it a 40 let's call it if
we're gonna roll it next time we're
gonna roll it but it's 14 yeah so come
here guys we're gonna go over in here
today and this is the price of a neon
it's $4.99 and we're gonna just you know
make it 5 13 because we're gonna add 14
dollars because we only have sent an
appreciating asset so let me just save
that I actually think we're gonna have
to uh we're gonna have to refresh the
webpage well so when I add this to my
cart like right now it says $4.99 but
when I add it to my cart it is five
hundred thirteen dollars up so scope is
uh I appreciate you joining me
today for this periscope remember your
yawns are an appreciating asset and they
just appreciated $14 thank you